

SHANE TSOSIE



OBJECTIVE

Strategic, graphic designer with an eye for innovation and perfection. Although my skill set is vast, my greatest expertise revolve in the worlds of social media, web banners, email blasts & print. My wish is to combine my knowledge and experience in these areas, to deliver the best creative to my employer's clients and their audiences.



928.853.9175

SHANETSOSIEDESIGN.COM

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/SHANETSOSIE

FACEBOOK.COM/SHANETSOSIEDESIGN

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS





Ai









CREATIVITY

COMMUNICATION

ORGANIZATION



TEAM PLAYER



EDUCATION

BFA IN VISUAL COMMUNICATION, MAY 2011 NORTHERN ARIZONA UNIVERSITY, FLAGSTAFF, AZ



EMPLOYMENT

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER (2011 - PRESENT)

- Meeting clients or account managers to discuss the business objectives and requirements of the job.
- Interpreting the client's business needs and developing a concept to suit their purpose.
- Proofreading to produce accurate and high-quality work.
- Working on layouts and art-working pages ready for print.

CREATIVE DIRECTOR BROOKS ADVERTISING (2018 - PRESENT)

- · Managed creative direction for all designers
- Planning new graphics, creative, and display layouts each month for each client
- Obtaining Approvals from clients on all creative and sending to appropriate vendors before deadline(s)
- Maintaining Websites of each client
- All graphic design for new client propositions

PRODUCTION MANAGER OUT THE WINDOW ADVERTISING (2014 - 2018)

- Managed creative direction for myself & multiple designers
- Worked directly with clients to develop & schedule design requests
- Oversaw, assisted & maintained quality control for fellow designers
- Developed advertising strategies & themes with clients
- Designed & produced on average 30 print/web based automotive & retail projects per week
- Adapted design & approach to changing market trends
- Maintained standards for over 25 different brands in all media produced

NATURAL FOOD MANAGER FRY'S FOOD & DRUG (2009 - 2016)

- In charge of receiving, stocking and display of organic and related product
- Maintains department cleanliness & provides world-class customer service
- Member of Fry's Cultural Council. The 'eyes & ears' between employee and manager relations